More

×

Search 

Privacy Policy
==============

**Effective:** July 22, 2021

Spice Box Product Development Ltd. (“Company” or “we” or “us” or “our” or “SpiceBox”) respects the privacy of its users (“user” or “you”) that use our website Spicebox.ca, including other media forms, media channels and also, Professor Maxwell’s 4D Science, Professor Maxwell’s 4D Chef, Professor Maxwell’s 4D Galaxy and Professor Maxwell's 4D Chemistry applications (“Apps”) on Google Play and Apple Store. The following Company privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) is designed to inform you, as a user of the Website and apps, about the types of information that Company may gather about or collect from you in connection with your use of the Website and Apps. It also is intended to explain the conditions under which Company uses and discloses that information, and your rights in relation to that information. Changes to this Privacy Policy are discussed at the end of this document. You can find the detail of the privacy policy via this link: [https://www.spicebox.ca/privacy-policy/](https://www.spicebox.ca/privacy-policy/)

Professor Maxwell’s 4D Science, Professor Maxwell’s 4D Chef, Professor Maxwell’s 4D Galaxy and Professor Maxwell's 4D Chemistry apps are intended for use by children, with parental participation and supervision. Please refer to the relevant sections in this policy for each. SpiceBox is committed to complying with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”) and the regulations of the Federal Trade Commission in the operation of our Apps.

BY USING OR ACCESSING THE WEBSITE/APPs, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY

**COLLECTING PERSONAL INFORMATION**

When you visit the Site, download our Android apps from Google Play as well as IOS apps on Apple Store, we collect certain information about your device, your interaction with the Site/App, and information necessary to process your purchases. We may also collect additional information if you contact us for customer support. In this Privacy Policy, we refer to any information that can uniquely identify an individual (including the information below) as “Personal Information”. See the list below for more information about what Personal Information we collect and why.

**Applications on Google Play and Apple Store**

Please note that Professor Maxwell’s 4D Science, Professor Maxwell’s 4D Chef, Professor Maxwell’s 4D Galaxy and Professor Maxwell's 4D Chemistry give users the ability to access videos and cameras for learning and engaging with VR technology. This feature is not stored on SpiceBox’s servers and is not shared with any unaffiliated third parties or other users. You may visit the device’s privacy settings to enable or disable the function at any time.

SpiceBox Product Development Ltd. does not collect personal information from children under the age of 13. We do not request that children provide us with personal information, and do not offer features that are intended to collect such information from children. If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 who has become a member of the Website or has otherwise transferred Personally-Identifying Information to the website or app, please contact Company using our contact information below to have that child's account terminated and information deleted.

**Web Cookies**

A “Web Cookie” is a string of information which assigns you a unique identification that a website stores on a user’s computer, and that the user’s browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the website. We use cookies on the Website to keep track of services you have used, to record registration information regarding your login name and password, to record your user preferences, to keep you logged into the Website and to facilitate purchase procedures. Company also uses Web Cookies to track the pages that users visit during each Website session, both to help Company improve users’ experiences and to help Company understand how the Website is being used. As with other Non- Personally-Identifying Information gathered from users of the Website, Company analyzes and discloses in aggregated form information gathered using Web Cookies, so as to help Company, its partners and others better understand how the Website is being used. COMPANY USERS WHO DO NOT WISH TO HAVE WEB COOKIES PLACED ON THEIR COMPUTERS SHOULD SET THEIR BROWSERS TO REFUSE WEB COOKIES BEFORE ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT CERTAIN FEATURES OF THE WEBSITE MAY NOT FUNCTION PROPERLY WITHOUT THE AID OF WEB COOKIES. WEBSITE USERS WHO REFUSE WEB COOKIES ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY.

The length of time that a cookie remains on your computer or mobile device depends on whether it is a “persistent” or “session” cookie. Session cookies last until you stop browsing and persistent cookies last until they expire or are deleted. Most of the cookies we use are persistent and will expire between 30 minutes and two years from the date they are downloaded to your device.

You can control and manage cookies in various ways. Please keep in mind that removing or blocking cookies can negatively impact your user experience and parts of our website may no longer be fully accessible.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can choose whether or not to accept cookies through your browser controls, often found in your browser’s “Tools” or “Preferences” menu. For more information on how to modify your browser settings or how to block, manage or filter cookies can be found in your browser’s help file or through such sites as [www.allaboutcookies.org](https://kenton12a.myshopify.com/admin/settings/www.allaboutcookies.org).

Additionally, please note that blocking cookies may not completely prevent how we share information with third parties such as our advertising partners. To exercise your rights or opt-out of certain uses of your information by these parties, please follow the instructions in the “Behavioural Advertising” section below.

**Behavioral Advertising**

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For example:

* We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site. You can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en).You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).
* We share information about your use of the Site, your purchases, and your interaction with our ads on other websites with our advertising partners. We collect and share some of this information directly with our advertising partners, and in some cases through the use of cookies or other similar technologies (which you may consent to, depending on your location).

For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work](http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work).

You can opt out of targeted advertising by:

* _FACEBOOK -_ [https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads](https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads)
* _GOOGLE -_ [https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous)
* _BING -_ [https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads](https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads)_\]_

_Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:_ [http://optout.aboutads.info/](http://optout.aboutads.info/)_._

**Third Party Service Providers**

We may use third-party vendors, including Google Ads and Google Analytics to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past activity on the Website and our apps. The information collected may be used to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand online activity. If you do not want any information to be collected and used by Google Analytics, you can install an opt-out in your web browser (https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) and/or opt out from Google Analytics for Display Advertising or the Google Display Network by using Google’s Ads Settings (www.google.com/settings/ads).

**Mobile Device Additional Terms**

• Mobile Device. If you use a mobile device to access the Website or download any of our applications from Google Play or Apple Store, we may collect device information (such as your mobile device ID, model and manufacturer), operating system, version information and IP address.

• Geo-Location Information. Unless we have received your prior consent, we do not access or track any location-based information from your mobile device at any time while downloading or using our mobile application or our services, except that it may be possible for Company to determine from an IP address the geographic location of your point of connectivity, in which case we may gather and use such general location data.

• Push Notifications. We send you push notifications if you choose to receive them, letting you know when someone has sent you a message or for other service-related matters. If you wish to opt-out from receiving these types of communications, you may turn them off in your device’s settings.

 **For example:**

Device information

* **Examples of Personal Information collected:** version of web browser, IP address, time zone, cookie information, what sites or products you view, search terms, and how you interact with the Site/App
* **Purpose of collection:** to load the Site/App accurately for you, and to perform analytics on Site usage to optimize our Site.
* **Source of collection:** Collected automatically when you access our Site using cookies, log files, tags, or pixels 
* **Disclosure for a business purpose:** shared with our web/app developers

Order information

* **Examples of Personal Information collected:** name, billing address, shipping address, payment information, email address, and phone number.
* **Purpose of collection:** to provide products or services to you to fulfill our contract, to process your payment information, arrange for shipping, and provide you with invoices and/or order confirmations, communicate with you, screen our orders for potential risk or fraud, and when in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.
* **Source of collection:** collected from you.
* **Disclosure for a business purpose:** shared with our web/app developers

Customer support information

* **Examples of Personal Information collected:** customer name and phone number
* **Purpose of collection:** to provide customer support.
* **Source of collection:** collected from you.
* **Disclosure for a business purpose:** shared with our web/app developers

**GENERAL USE**

Company uses the Personally-Identifying Information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Website (1) to deliver the products and services that you have requested; (2) to manage your account and provide you with customer support; (3) to communicate with you by email, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us, our affiliate companies or other third parties; (4) to develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on the Website and other sites; (5) to resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems; (6) to measure consumer interest in our services; (7) to inform you of updates; (8) to customize your experience; (9) to detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; (10) to enforce our Terms of Use; and (11) to do as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems. In particular, we may examine your Personally-Identifying Information to identify users using multiple user IDs or aliases. We may compare and review your Personally-Identifying Information for accuracy and to detect errors and omissions. We may use financial information or payment method to process payment for any purchases made on the Website, enroll you in the discount, rebate, and other programs in which you elect to participate, to protect against or identify possible fraudulent transactions and otherwise as needed to manage our business.

 **SECURITY**

Spice Box Product Development Ltd. takes the security of your Personally-Identifying Information seriously and use reasonable electronic, personnel and physical measures to protect it from loss, theft, alteration or misuse. However, please be advised that even the best security measures cannot fully eliminate all risks. We cannot guarantee that only authorized persons will view your information. We are not responsible for third-party circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures.  
We are dedicated to protect all information on the Website as is necessary. However, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your Personally-Identifying Information by keeping your password confidential. You should change your password immediately if you believe someone has gained unauthorized access to it or your account. If you lose control of your account, you should notify us immediately.

**PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES**

Company may, in its sole discretion, change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any and all changes to Company’s Privacy Policy will be reflected on this page and the date new versions are posted will be stated at the top of this Privacy Policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. Users should regularly check this page for any changes to this Privacy Policy. Company will always post new versions of the Privacy Policy on the Website. However, Company may, as determined in its discretion, decide to notify users of changes made to this Privacy Policy via email or otherwise. Accordingly, it is important that users always maintain and update their contact information.

**CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine The Light" law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about the Personally-Identifying Information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of the Personally-Identifying Information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared Personally-Identifying Information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to our privacy officer as listed below.

**DO-NOT-TRACK POLICY**  
Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. Because there is not yet a common understanding of how to interpret the DNT signal, the Website currently does not respond to DNT browser signals or mechanisms

**RETENTION**

Spice Box Product Development Ltd. only retains the data collected pursuant to this Privacy Policy for the period of time necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. When you place an order through the spicebox.ca or use our app on google or apple store, we will retain your Personal Information for our records unless and until you ask us to erase this information. For more information on your right of erasure, please see the ‘Your rights’ section below.

**CCPA**

If you are a resident of California, you have the right to access the Personal Information we hold about you (also known as the ‘Right to Know’), to port it to a new service, and to ask that your Personal Information be corrected, updated, or erased. If you would like to exercise these rights, please contact us through the contact information below. If you would like to designate an authorized agent to submit these requests on your behalf, please contact us at **ecommerce@spiceboxbooks.com** or by mail using the details provided below: **Spice Box Product Development Ltd.** 12171 Horseshoe Way, Richmond, BC V7A 4V4, Canada

**CONTACT**

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at [ecommerce@spiceboxbooks.com](mailto:ecommerce@spiceboxbooks.com)**, or at 604 272 2670** or by mail using the details provided below: **Spice Box Product Development Ltd.** 12171 Horseshoe Way, Richmond, BC V7A 4V4, Canada

OK

##### COMPANY

##### OUR CATEGORIES

##### [CONTACT US](https://www.spicebox.ca/contact-us/)

##### Let's Stay Connected

##### [](https://www.spicebox.ca/)

* SpiceBox Product Development Ltd  
    12171 Horseshoe Way  
    Richmond, BC V7A 4V4  
    Canada

© 2024 SpiceBox Product Development Canada.

Powered by [BigCommerce](https://www.bigcommerce.com/?utm_source=merchant&utm_medium=poweredbyBC). Theme by [Papathemes](https://papathemes.com/?utm_source=merchant&utm_medium=poweredbyBC).

Categories

* Shop by Brands

* Categories
* Account
* Contact

* More

Account

* Sign In
    
    Email Address: 
    
    Password:
